Full Stack Python Developer

Andy Thomas

512-436-5120



I became obsessed with coding while studying for an Insurance Data Analytics Designation with my previous employer. During the pandemic, I guit a comfortable job to pursue a career as a developer in Big Data and Automation. I'm self-taught with a proven history as a high-performing, self-starter. I've spent the last two years building interesting projects, learning relevant skills, and taking on freelance opportunities by helping professionals automate their daily tasks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SCS Team Lead

Amica Mutual Insurance (5 Years)

05/2019 - 07/2020

Austin, TX

Tasks

- Attended 4 career fairs with senior-level managers to recruit new
- Interviewed candidates with leadership team to determine behavioral and cultural fits
- Managed a team of sales and underwriting professionals

SaaS Ambassador | Salesforce | Guidewire

Amica Mutual Insurance

09/2018 - 05/2019 Austin, TX

Tasks

- Worked directly with dev team on design interface
- Reported bugs/errors to developers during deployment
- Trained an office of 70+ employees and managers on Salesforce and Guidewire software

Corporate Trainer

Amica Mutual Insurance

03/2018 - 09/2018

Austin, TX

Tasks

Led 4 training classes bringing new hires from the onboarding process to floor readiness

Senior Sales Representative

Amica Mutual Insurance

12/2017 - 05/2018 Austin, TX

Achievements/Tasks

- Met or exceeded all sales requirements while taking on additional responsibilities
- Top Level Binding Authority: Auto (no restrictions), Home (up to \$800k Cov. A), PUP (up to \$2mm)

Sales Representative

Amica Mutual Insurance

05/2015 - 12/2017 Austin, TX

EDUCATION

O BBA, Finance

Texas Tech Universtiy

Lubbock, TX

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Andy Thomas Professional Website

- Built, Deployed and Run by Andy Thomas
- Skills Applied: Python, Flask, HTML, CSS and Bootstrap
- View website below: https://andythomasdotpy.herokuapp.com/

Whisky-Valuator

- I collect rare and interesting whiskey but needed an easy way to value my bottles
- This program scrapes a secondary auction site, converts the currency in real time (using an X-Rate API) and creates an easy to read chart to track pricing trends
- Skills Applied: Python, Beautiful Soup, HTML, REST API, Pandas, Matplotlib and Seaborn
- View source code below: https://github.com/andythomasdotpy/whiskey_valuator

ACHIEVEMENTS

Trained the 2019 Bronze and Silver Award Winners during my time as Corporate Trainer

Sales Excellence Awards - Bronze Winner 2017 #3 in sales (of 58 reps) with Amica Mutual Insurance

Sales Excellence Awards - Bronze Winner 2016 #3 in sales (of 42 reps) with Amica Mutual Insurance